The Reese Family Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
The Reese Family Papers
1692 – 2003
1785 – 1975
NPkMC-322-011
42 linear feet
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
The Reese Family
Insert abstract here!
Collection Overview
The papers of Reese family document the professional and personal lives of several of the ancestors of Frances Gallatin Stevens Reese and her husband, Willis Livingston Mesier Reese. The papers contain indentures, personal, political, and business correspondence, military documents, manuscripts of prose and poetry, scrapbooks, bills of lading, invoices, promissory notes, canceled checks, financial ledgers, diaries, passports, newspaper clippings and photographs.
The following explains some of the relationships among the creators of the Reese Family Papers:
Ebenezer Stevens (1751-1823) was the father of Samuel Stevens (1785-1844), Byam Kerby Stevens (1797-1869) and Henry Hewgill Stevens (1797-1869), who was the father of Francis K. Stevens. Byam Kerby Stevens married Frances Gallatin, and was the father of Alexander Henry Stevens (1834-1916), who married Mary Alleyne Otis (born circa 1840s). Alexander Henry Stevens was the father of Mary (May) Otis Stevens (1862-1950), Francis Kerby Stevens (1877-1945), who married Elizabeth Shaw Oliver (1873-1951), and Emily Stevens Ladenberg (born circa 1870s). Their daughter was Frances Gallatin Stevens (1917-2003), who married Willis Livingston Mesier Reese. Emily Stevens Ladenburg married Adolph Ladenberg (?-1896) and gave birth to Eugenie “May” Ladenberg Davie who was the head of the Woman’s Auxiliary of the Republican Party in the 1930s. Civil War General and Stove inventor John Finley Rathbone (1819-1901) married Mary Allen Baker (1826-1902) and was the father of Marion Rathbone (1847-1926). Daniel Augustus Oliver (1817-1850) married Elizabeth Willard Shaw (?-1850) and was the father of Robert Shaw Oliver (1847-1935), who served as Assistant Secretary of War under President Theodore Roosevelt. Robert Shaw Oliver and Marion Rathbone married and gave birth to Elizabeth Shaw Oliver and John Rathbone Oliver (1872-1943).
Acquisitions Information
The Reese Family Papers were donated to Marist College by the Reese family in 2006.
Historical Note
The ancestors of Frances Gallatin Stevens Reese (1917-2003) and her husband, Willis Livingston Mesier Reese (1913-1990), were prominent residents of Dutchess County, New York for many generations. Descended from the Reese, Willis and Mesier families, Willis Reese was the Charles Evans Hughes Professor Emeritus of Law, as well as the Director of the Parker School of Foreign and Comparative Law at Columbia Law School. Frances Reese, known as Franny, was the daughter of Francis Kerby Stevens (1877-1873) and Elizabeth Shaw Oliver (1873-1951). Franny was a founder of Scenic Hudson, which, beginning in the 1960s, fought for 17 years to prevent a power plant from being built on Storm King Mountain in New York.
The Stevens family can trace their lineage to Ebenezer Stevens (1751-1823), born in Roxbury, Massachusetts. He was a participant in the Boston Tea Party, commissioned as a first lieutenant in the Artillery in 1775, and fought in the Battle of Bunker Hill. George Washington selected Ebenezer to raise battalions against Quebec to join the expedition against Canada. Ebenezer was present at the surrender of the British General Burgoyne at Saratoga, New York, on October 17, 1777. He served under the French general the Marquis de Lafayette in Virginia. He was later transferred to the New York artillery and in 1781 was one of the commanders at the siege of Yorktown. By 1805 he had risen to the rank of Major General and was involved in the defense of New York during the War of 1812. After his military career Stevens was a successful merchant in New York and a member of the state Assembly.
Ebenezer Stevens’s descendants were also successful in their pursuits. Byam Kerby Stevens married into the Gallatin family, New York bankers who helped found the Astor Trust Company. Alexander Henry Stevens was the Vice President of the Astor Trust Company, and his son, Francis Kerby Stevens was successful in both the New York real estate industry and with his dairy farm in Gladstone, New Jersey. His real estate business had been in the family since its creation by Francis’s great-uncle Samuel Stevens. Francis’s sister, Emily Stevens married into the Ladenberg banking family and gave birth to Eugenie “May” Ladenberg Davie who became an active member of the Republican Party and was the head of the Woman’s Auxiliary during Wendell Willkie’s campaign to unseat Franklin D. Roosevelt in 1940.
On her mother’s side, Frances Gallatin Stevens Reese is descended from Daniel Augustus Oliver and John Finley Rathbone. Daniel Oliver’s son, Robert Shaw Oliver served in the Civil War, rising to the rank of General after the conflict. He was named Assistant Secretary of War in 1903 under Theodore Roosevelt and served into the administration of William Howard Taft. John Rathbone entered the booming Albany stove industry and in 1845 built the largest stove factory in the world whose products were found as far away as the Middle East. He served as a General during the Civil War and was so successful recruiting and organizing local troops that he rose to the rank of Major General after the war. John Rathbone also ran for mayor in 1864 and became one of Albany’s leading philanthropists as the library at the University of Rochester is named for him.
Despite these successes, the most exceptional member of the family may have been Frances Reese’s uncle, John Rathbone Oliver. Born in 1872 to Robert Shaw Oliver and Marion Rathbone, who was the daughter of John Finley Rathbone, John Oliver was successful as a teacher, minister, doctor and writer. After touring Europe as a teenager he was the valedictorian in 1894 as he graduated Harvard as a Master of Arts. Six years later he enrolled in a seminary and was ordained as an Episcopal priest serving in Philadelphia and Albany. At 32 he left for Austria and studied medicine, obtaining his medical degree at the Royal Academy at Innsbruck. He then served as a surgeon in the Austrian Army until a heart attack in 1915, a condition that denied him the chance to serve in the U.S. Army Medical Corps as his application was refused in 1917. After the war Oliver returned to the priesthood and served in Baltimore at Johns Hopkins where he became involved with prison inmates and became the Chief Medical Officer of the Baltimore court system while earning his Doctor of Philosophy in 1927. He later became a consulting psychiatrist and a professor of history of medicine at the University of Maryland medical school. Oliver was also a prolific writer, as can be seen in this collection, his novel, Victor and Victim, came within one vote of winning the Pulitzer Prize in 1929.
Restrictions to Access
There are no restrictions on this collection
Arrangement of the Collection
These records are organized into nine series. 1) The Reese Family, has 6 subseries, suberies 1.5 has eight subseries, subseries 1.6 has 6 subseries, sub-subseries 1.6.5 has four subseries, 2) The Mesier Family, has five subseries, 3) The Willis Family, has three subseries, 4) The Stevens Family, has nine subseries, subseries 4.2 has five subserues and one sub-subseries, subseries 4.4 has three subseries, subseries 4.6 has four subseries, subseries 4.7 has three subseries, subseries 4.8 has three subseries, subseries 4.8 has five subseries, 5)The Davie Family, has one subseries and one sub-subseries, 6) The Rathbone Family, has two subseries, 7) The Oliver Family, has four subseries, subseries 7.2 has two subseries, subseries 7.3 has four subseries, subseries 7.4 has 8 subseries, 8) Graphic Materials, has six subseries, subseries 8.2 has seven subseries, 9) Administratige files has two subseries
Series and subseries are divided by family, person, and/or subject.
- The Reese Family, 1761 - 2003; 1; Boxes: 1 - 14 Folders: 1 - 19, 1 - 21, 1 - 32, 1 - 47, 1 - 18, 1 - 30, 1 - 37, 1 - 26, 1 - 14, 1 - 18, 1 - 26, 1 - 36, 1 - 14, 1 - 16, 1 - 17
  Series contains correspondence, materials pretaining to business and finance, miscellany, materials from M.A. Reese, Willis L.M. Reese,
  Arrangement: Subject
  - Correspondence, 1859 - 1920; 1.1; Box: 1 Folders: 1 - 11
    - Correspondence to Henry Suydam from John J. Reese, George Bickham Reese and E. Livingston Reese, 1859 June 14 - 1861 August 7 (Folder 1, Box 1)
    - Correspondence to Henry [Reese?] from Mrs. Amos T. Newbold, 1881 April 27 (Folder 2, Box 1)
    - Correspondence to Henry Reese from Henry G. Satterlee, 1881 May 10 (Folder 3, Box 1)
    - Correspondence to Mrs. William H. Reese, 1885 August 25 (Folder 4, Box 1)
    - Correspondence to mother from Willis, 1882 May 23 (Folder 5, Box 1)
    - Jacob R. Reese and W. Henry Reese (receipt for money received from Henry Mesier, Executor of the Margaret Reese estate), 1896 August 8 (Folder 6, Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 1898 October 4 (Folder 7, Box 1)
    - Correspondence to Henry [Reese?] from Lewis Marshall, 1899 February 2 - March 2 (Folder 8, Box 1)
    - Correspondence to William H. Reese from Henry F. Snyder of the Surrogate’s Court, Albany, N.Y., 1900 February 19 (Folder 9, Box 1)
    - Correspondence to W. Willis Reese from William E. Verplanck, circa 1920 December 21 (Folder 10, Box 1)
    - Correspondence, undated (Folder 11, Box 1)
  - Business and finance, 1868 - 1890; 1.2; Box: 1 Folders: 12 - 19
    - W. Henry Reese, Banker (account books for Julia G. Bowdoin and Charles W. Clark), 1878 - 1881 (Folder 12, Box 1)
    - W. Henry Reese, Banker (account books for Henry Mesier and Henry G. Satterlee), 1880 - 1881 (Folder 13, Box 1)
    - W. Henry Reese, Banker (account books for Richard J. Van Dewater, Sarah L. Van Wyck and Zion P. E. Church), 1881 (Folder 14, Box 1)
    - W. Henry Reese, Banker (estate of Charles R. […]), 1882 (Folder 15, Box 1)
    - Estate of John Livingston Reese, 1900 June 7 (Folder 16, Box 1)
    - George Bickham Reese (receipt for money received from Henry Mesier, Executor of the Margaret Reese estate), 1868 July 18 (Folder 17, Box 1)
    - Checking account book (Fulton National Bank), 1880 - 1881 (Folder 18, Box 1)
    - Checking account book, 1890 (Folder 19, Box 1)
  - Miscellany, 1761 - 1925; 1.3; Boxes: 2 - 3 Folders: 1 - 21, 1 - 4
    - Expenditures book, 1850 - 1879 (Folder 1, Box 2)
    - Newspaper clippings (includes clippings regarding Doctor John Livingston Reese and the marriage of David Augustus Clarkson and Maria Mesier Reese [1898 October]), 1898 - 1902, circa 1960s (Folder 2, Box 2)
    - Billfolds [2 items], 1825 - 1826 (Folder 3, Box 2)
    - Bernard Golden (certificate exempting Golden from military service “…by reason of having furnished an accepted alien substitute…”, 1864 August 24 (Folder 4, Box 2)
    - Bernard Golden (last will and testament), 1914 September 10 (Folder 5, Box 2)
    - “The Silver Wedding” (poem dedicated to Mrs. P. S. Van Rensselaer on the 25th anniversary of her wedding), 1864 October 17 (Folder 6, Box 2)
    - Poem dedicated to Willis Reese on his 6th birthday written by Aunt Alice, 1919 June 16 (Folder 7, Box 2)
    - Irving Grinnell (resolutions in memoriam from Zion Church, Wappingers Falls, New York and the Trustees of The Grinnell Library Association, Wappingers Falls, New York), 1921 June 11-14 (Folder 8, Box 2)
    - Land plot map (includes plots belonging to Mr. Grinnell, Mr. Reese and Mr. Satterlee among others), undated (Folder 9, Box 2)
    - List of articles sent, circa late 1800s (Folder 10, Box 2)
    - Place cards (used Augusta Bliss Reese), undated (Folder 11, Box 2)
    - William Willis Reese (school documents, including report cards and compositions), 1883 - 1885 (Folder 12, Box 2)
    - Estate of John Livingston Reese, 1899 January 31 (Folder 13, Box 2)
    - William Willis Reese (obituary), undated (Folder 14, Box 2)
    - Sketch of Dietrick Reese seal, undated (Folder 15, Box 2)
    - William Willis Reese (confirmation certificate from the Diocese of New Hampshire, 1885 May 14 (Folder 16, Box 2)
    - Diary, 1914 (Folder 17, Box 2)
    - Yale University commencement program, 1897 June 13 (Folder 18, Box 2)
    - “The Game of Squash” by Eustace Miles, M.A., 1901 (Folder 19, Box 2)
    - Proclamation and Accession to the throne of George III [photocopy], 1761 January 17 (Folder 20, Box 2)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1840 August 27 - October 6, 1854 December 15 (Folder 21, Box 2)
    - Carl Haller Ill (lecture notes), circa 1914 - 1916 (Folder 1, Box 3)
    - Carl Haller Ill (lecture notes), circa 1914 - 1916 (Folder 2, Box 3)
    - Carl Haller Ill - Princeton University scrapbook (includes ephemera, photographs, clippings, school documents and correspondence), circa 1909 - 1917 (Folder 3, Box 3)
    - Carl Haller Ill (miscellaneous papers), circa 1917 - 1925 (Folder 4, Box 3)
  - M.A. Reese, 1870 - 1928; 1.4; Box: 3 Folders: 5 - 9
    - Letter from M.A. Reese to her parents, 1892 May 20 (Folder 5, Box 3)
    - Notebook 1 - Labeled M. A. Reese, 1898 (Folder 6, Box 3)
    - Documents found in Notebook 1, 1870 - 1903 (Folder 7, Box 3)
    - Notebook 2, circa 1920s (Folder 8, Box 3)
    - Documents found in Notebook 2, 1917 - 1928 (Folder 9, Box 3)
  - Willis L.M. Reese, 1902- 1997; 1.5; Boxes: 3 - 6 Folders: 10 - 32, 1 - 47, 1 - 18, 1 - 30
    Series contains personal documents, documents pretaining to military service, materials pretaining to legal career, school documents, club materials and speeches, matierlas frolm thje Millbrook School, newspaper clippings, and miscellany
    - Personal documents, 1938 - 1942; 1.5.1; Box: 3 Folders: 10 - 26
      - Letters from Willis Reese to his parents, 1938 (Folder 10, Box 3)
      - Letters from Willis Reese’s father, W. Willis Reese, 1938 (Folder 11, Box 3)
      - Notes, 1938 (Folder 12, Box 3)
      - Real Estate Mortgages, circa 1938 (Folder 13, Box 3)
      - Documents concerning the reservations and cancellation of Willis Reese’s trip abroad, 1938 (Folder 14, Box 3)
      - Letter to Willis Reese’s father, W. Willis Reese asking him to be a reference on his son’s lease, 1938, June 24 (Folder 15, Box 3)
      - Moving receipt of Mrs. Willis Reese, 1938 June (Folder 16, Box 3)
      - Two letters to Willis Reese from MacNeil Mitchell, 1938 (Folder 17, Box 3)
      - Oath of Willis Reese to Judge Thomas W. Swan and relating correspondence, 1938 October 5 (Folder 18, Box 3)
      - Willis Reese’s Application to the Bar, Affidavits of character, 1938 November (Folder 19, Box 3)
      - Letter from Willis Reese to Otto, concerning occupancy tax, 1939 July 13 (Folder 20, Box 3)
      - Letters recommending Willis L.W. Reese to the Bar, 1940 (Folder 21, Box 3)
      - Letter from Colonel Chauncey L. Fenton concerning a position in the Judge Advocate General’s Reserve, 1940, November 5 (Folder 22, Box 3)
      - Letter concerning Willis Reese’s will, 1940, November 22 (Folder 23, Box 3)
      - Letters from Colonel Chauncey L. Fenton concerning a teaching position at the United States Military Academy at West Point, 1941 (Folder 24, Box 3)
      - Letter of recommendation from Lieutenant Colonel F.J. Pearson, 1941 December 30 (Folder 25, Box 3)
      - Letter from Willis Reese’s secretary to the Department of Justice, 1942 February 16 (Folder 26, Box 3)
      - Letter in French to Willis Reese from Ralph Peer, undated (Folder 27, Box 3)
    - Military service, 1943 - 1952; 1.5.1; Box: 3 Folders: 27 - 32
      - Documents pertaining to Military service, 1943 (Folder 28, Box 3)
      - Documents pertaining to Military service, 1944 (Folder 29, Box 3)
      - Documents pertaining to Military service, 1945 (Folder 30, Box 3)
      - Documents pertaining to Military service, 1946 (Folder 31, Box 3)
      - Documents pertaining to Military service, 1952 (Folder 32, Box 3)
    - Legal career, 1945 - 1973; 1.5.3; Box: 4 Folders: 1 - 24
      - Documents pertaining to Willis Reese’s leaving of Winthrop, Stimson, Putman& Roberts, 1945 (Folder 1, Box 4)
      - Documents pertaining to Willis Reese’s leaving of Winthrop, Stimson, Putman& Roberts, 1945 (Folder 2, Box 4)
      - Postwar letter from “Bob” to Yorke, Howard and Willis [Reese?], 1945 (Folder 3, Box 4)
      - Documents pertaining to the appointment of Willis Reese to the Law faculty at Columbia University, 1945 (Folder 4, Box 4)
      - Letter to Willis Reese from Frank R. Kenison, Chief Justice of the Supreme Court of the State of New Hampshire concerning the application of a law, 1959 January 30 (Folder 5, Box 4)
      - Columbia University Bulletin, sixty-second series, number 7: The Study of Law at Columbia, Willis Reese on cover, 1962 February 17 (Folder 6, Box 4)
      - Letter from the University of Miami offering Willis Reese the post of Dean of the School of Law, 1964 May 1 (Folder 7, Box 4)
      - Biographical sketch of Willis Livingston Mesier Reese’s law career by G. Van Hecke, written for Willis Reese’s honorary doctorate of law, circa 1972 (Folder 8, Box 4)
      - Letter from Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller appointing Willis Reese as Chairman of the Law Revision Commission, 1973 September 11 (Folder 9, Box 4)
      - Press release detailing the acceptance of John W. MacDonald’s resignation as Chairman of the State Law Revision Committee by Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller and his appointment of Willis Reese, contains both letters from MacDonald and Rockefeller, 3 copies, 1973 September 11 (Folder 10, Box 4)
      - Letter of Congratulations from T.N. Hurd, Secretary to the Governor on Willis Reeses’s appointment as Chairman of the State Law Revision Committee, also newspaper clipping from the Poughkeepsie journal dated the next day, 1973 September 12 (Folder 11, Box 4)
      - Letter of Congratulations from Whitney North Seymour, on Willis Reeses’s appointment as Chairman of the State Law Revision Committee, 1973 September 12 (Folder 12, Box 4)
      - Letter of Congratulations from Jason R. Gettinger, Assistant Counsel to the Governor, on Willis Reeses’s appointment as Chairman of the State Law Revision Committee, 1973 September 13 (Folder 13, Box 4)
      - Letter of Congratulations from Theodore R. Kupferman, New York State Supreme Justice, on Willis Reeses’s appointment as Chairman of the State Law Revision Committee, 1973 September 13 (Folder 14, Box 4)
      - Letter of Congratulations from William Hughes Mulligan, United States Circuit Judge, on Willis Reeses’s appointment as Chairman of the State Law Revision Committee, 1973 September 13 (Folder 15, Box 4)
      - Letter of Congratulations from Bernard S. Meyer on Willis Reeses’s appointment as Chairman of the State Law Revision Committee, 1973 September 14 (Folder 16, Box 4)
      - Letter of Congratulations from Arthur H. Schwartz on Willis Reeses’s appointment as Chairman of the State Law Revision Committee, 1973 September 14 (Folder 17, Box 4)
      - Letter of Congratulations from Judge Edward D. Re on Willis Reeses’s appointment as Chairman of the State Law Revision Committee, with newspaper clipping, 1973 September 18 (Folder 18, Box 4)
      - Letter of Congratulations from Daniel Martin Freeman on Willis Reeses’s appointment as Chairman of the State Law Revision Committee, 1973 November 12 (Folder 19, Box 4)
      - Letter of Congratulations from Albert G. Redpath on Willis Reeses’s appointment as Chairman of the State Law Revision Committee, 1973 November 13 (Folder 20, Box 4)
      - Letter of Congratulations from Edwin O. Tilton on Willis Reeses’s appointment as Chairman of the State Law Revision Committee, 1973 November 17 (Folder 21, Box 4)
      - Letter of Congratulations from New York Supreme Court Justice Bertram Garnett on Willis Reeses’s appointment as Chairman of the State Law Revision Committee, 1973 November 20 (Folder 22, Box 4)
      - Letter of Congratulations from “Lola” on Willis Reeses’s appointment as Chairman of the State Law Revision Committee, undated (Folder 23, Box 4)
      - Christmas card from Dean and Mrs. William C. Warren showing Kent Hall, where Willis’s first offices were, undated (Folder 24, Box 4)
    - School documents, 1925 - 1929; 1.5.4; Boxes: 4 Folders: 25 - 36
      - Willis Reese’s Notebook from St. Paul’s School, 1925 - 1926 (Folder 25, Box 4)
      - Report Card of Willis Reese at St. Paul’s School, 1926 (Folder 26, Box 4)
      - Report Card of Willis Reese at St. Paul’s School, 1928 (Folder 27, Box 4)
      - Report Card of Willis Reese at St. Paul’s School, 1929 (Folder 28, Box 4)
      - Report Card of Willis Reese at St. Paul’s School, 1929 (Folder 29, Box 4)
      - Willis Reese’s Algebra Exams at St. Paul’s School [removed from Notebook - File 1.5.4.4.25], 1926 - 1927 (Folder 30, Box 4)
      - Willis Reese’s English Exams at St. Paul’s School [removed from Notebook - File 1.5.4.4.25], 1926 - 1927 (Folder 31, Box 4)
      - Willis Reese’s French Exams at St. Paul’s School [removed from Notebook - File 1.5.4.4.25], 1926 - 1927 (Folder 32, Box 4)
      - Willis Reese’s History Exams at St. Paul’s School [removed from Notebook - File 1.5.4.4.25], 1926 - 1927 (Folder 33, Box 4)
      - Willis Reese’s Latin Exams at St. Paul’s School [removed from Notebook - File 1.5.4.4.25], 1926 - 1927 (Folder 34, Box 4)
      - Willis Reese’s Sacred Studies Exams at St. Paul’s School [removed from Notebook - File 1.5.4.4.25], 1926 - 1927 (Folder 35, Box 4)
      - Willis Reese’s Science Exams at St. Paul’s School [removed from Notebook - File 1.5.4.4.25], 1926 - 1927 (Folder 36, Box 4)
    - Clubs and speeches, 1938 - 1970; 1.5.5; Box: 4 Folders: 37 - 47
      - St. Paul’s School, Alumni Association, 1938 April (Folder 37, Box 4)
      - The Century Association, 1951 January 11 (Folder 38, Box 4)
      - The American Society of International Law, 1954 January 29 (Folder 39, Box 4)
      - The Law Book Department of Little, Brown and Company, Editorial Board, 1956, April 23 (Folder 40, Box 4)
      - The American Law Institute, 1957, 1970 (Folder 41, Box 4)
      - Church of the Transfiguration, 1964 (Folder 42, Box 4)
      - Hague Academy of International Law, 1964 (Folder 43, Box 4)
      - The Foundation Press, Inc., 1965 February 8 (Folder 44, Box 4)
      - Wappingers Historical Society, 1969 (Folder 45, Box 4)
      - Speech at the Villanova Law Review’s Ninth Annual Banquet, “Reminiscences of a Reporter”, 1964 April 18 (Folder 46, Box 4)
      - Speech for the United Nations Association, “The World Court - Its Weaknesses& Its Future”, undated (Folder 47, Box 4)
    - Millbrook School, 1961 - 1974; 1.5.6; Box: 5 Folders: 1 - 10
      - Program for L.A.W.S. Conference, Willis Reese speaks, with doodles, undated (Folder 1, Box 5)
      - Letter from Headmaster Donn Wright detailing fires started by students and their arrests for arson, 1971 November 11 (Folder 2, Box 5)
      - Millbrook School Commencement Programs, Willis Reese speaks for the Trustees, 1969, 1973 (Folder 3, Box 5)
      - Issues of “The Mill,” featuring writings by students, 1963, 1970 - 1971 (Folder 4, Box 5)
      - The Tamarack Supplement, detailing Millbrook’s sports teams featuring John Reese for Tennis, 1961 (Folder 5, Box 5)
      - The Millbrook Bulletin, 1969 - 1970 (Folder 6, Box 5)
      - Millbrook School Calendar, 1972 - 1974 (Folder 7, Box 5)
      - Millbrook School, booklet of photos, undated (Folder 8, Box 5)
      - “The Silo,” front page article detailing Willis Reese’s elevation to Head of the Millbrook School’s Board of Trustees [another copy in File 1.5.6.5.10], 1968 March 12 (Folder 9, Box 5)
      - Issues of “The Silo,” Millbrook School newspaper, 1965 - 1973 (Folder 10, Box 5)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1950 - 1973; 1.5.7; Boxes: 5 - 6 Folders: 11 - 18, 1 - 2
      - From the Columbia Law School News, concerning Willis Reese, 1973 (Folder 11, Box 5)